One day I will build a big mansion for you.
I don't want a mansion.
I want a home. Our home.
One two three four
How can I tell you why I love you, I can't even if I try.
My eyes express the feelings of my heart to you...
You know English right?
Then sing an English song.
What does Parthavi mean?
Atom bomb. The day it will explode we all will die.
What did the doctor say?
It's a heart attack, could slip into a coma.
Take care.
Why are you acting smart since yesterday?
Nothing. - Why aren't you looking at me?
I am looking at you. - Why aren't you looking properly?
Yesterday you had braids in your hair wearing a multi-color dress.
Today you are in a suit with open hair, If this isn't proper what is?
Madhu... I love you...
...you also say.
I am feeling shy. - Shy!
I'll give you a tight slap...
I love you too.
I want a pappi (kiss)...
Puppy?
You mean a dog's baby?
Long live Ratan Singh
Madhu..... leave him....
I will shoot myself.
I made a mistake by coming with you here.
Huge mistake.
One two three four...
...how do I tell you how much I love you, I will never be able to.
You don't know, you don't know.
Dhadak
so who will cook in the new house, you or me?
You! And make it calorie free I want to stay slim.